The last thing that we're going to do to complete this look is we're going to use a little bit of gloss.
I'm going to use this shade right here.
It has a little bit of shine to it, a little bit of sparkle.
That's going to go really well the nice glowing look that we've given her skin.
So we're going to take a little bit of this on our lip brush.
We're just going to do it right in the center of the lips.
Give the lips a poutier look and give the lips a little bit of sheen.
So by doing the lip gloss just right in the center of the lip it gives a nice brightness and a nice shine.
So it catches the light and it will make the lips look a lot fuller.
So you can see it gives her a nice little pop of shine right in the center of the lips.
It makes the lips look a little bit poutier.
It also balances the rest of the look really well.
By blending the nice dewy glow that we've given her skin with the lips.
So this is how you would want to complete this baby doll make up look.